{
    "subject": "resource/Sussex_Skyhawks",
    "predicate": "property/owner",
    "object": "resource/Floyd_Hall",
    "human_readable": "The owner of Sussex Skyhawks is Floyd Hall.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.93842613697052,
            "question": "Who owns the Sussex Skyhawks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9177459478378296,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Floyd Hall and the Sussex Skyhawks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8924708366394043,
            "question": "What is the name of the owner of the Sussex Skyhawks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8021058440208435,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Floyd Hall and the Sussex Skyhawks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.792883038520813,
            "question": "Who is responsible for the Sussex Skyhawks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.786642849445343,
            "question": "Is Floyd Hall the owner of a sports team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7802760601043701,
            "question": "Name the sports team owned by Floyd Hall."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.764907956123352,
            "question": "To which team does Floyd Hall belong as an owner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6021334528923035,
            "question": "What team does Floyd Hall own?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5941723585128784,
            "question": "Does Floyd Hall have any ownership in sports teams?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The owner of Sussex Skyhawks is Floyd Hall.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6256_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What team does Floyd Hall own?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6256_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which team does Floyd Hall belong as an owner?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6256_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the sports team owned by Floyd Hall.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6256_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6256_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6256_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6256_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6256_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6256_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6256_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6256_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6256_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6256_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6256_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all three documents mention Floyd Hall as the owner of the Sussex Skyhawks, with document 1 mentioning that he was trying to sell the team and document 3 mentioning that his firm owns the Skyhawks."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The owner of Sussex Skyhawks is Floyd Hall.\" For instance, from `49.txt`, it states: \"The Skyhawks were owned and managed by Floyd Hall, the former CEO of Kmart (1995-2001) and his son Larry Hall.\" This directly indicates that Floyd Hall was one of the owners of the Sussex Skyhawks."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}